[Music] good early morning Squad from um Golden
British Columbia base of kicking horse mountain
resort I feel like I've been talking about this
trip really ever since kind of the start of the
year but I am up here for a 3day heli skiing trip
with CMH pcel this has been like a totally sort
of sponsored shindig they flew a bunch of us
up here they put us into lodging they've kind
of taken care of the whole itinerary and the
plan is to highlight and showcase the sort of
heli skiing option that CMH has and just enjoy
3 days up here in the mountains hopefully get
in the heli hopefully ski a little bit so it
is safe to say I am just wildly stoked to be
here um this kind of a really cool crew Abe
kovitz is up here from GoPro zadia um Caleb
Pharaoh so very fun group of people and
we should have 3 days beautiful weather
to uh just ski a little bit so we have like
a 6:30 call time to head over to the lodge so
that's what we're going to do this is my room
nice king-size bed coffee maker no [Applause]
[Music] [Applause] [Music] complaints [Music]
[Music] we're going to it's be interesting we'll
probably get to see some big avalanch we do some
Avalanche observing just but we're to uh limit
our exposure we got a pretty Limited ski program
is what I'm trying to stay ex so we rated our
Hazard you know it's sort of in this there's a
fiveo scale one being low five being extreme and
uh the last few weeks we've been sort of dancing
around that considerable three Mark we've been uh
witnessing Avalanches thinking that it's pretty
there's been a lot of skier Associated avalan
throughout the province whether they be like
remoting from a distance but it's been pretty
active but not like nuclear active and uh and
so this morning with it like it didn't even freeze
up 3,000 M or 2400 M last night was above zero so
we didn't get any do the overnight recovery and
then as the sun comes up today so you know when
when the water freezes it bonds and so now we're
we're in this period where it just hasn't had that
opportunity for overnight recovery so by the time
we get out there at 10:30 11:00 it's already going
to be sort of warming up and free water I'm a I'm
a filmmaker at GoPro I also like to dabble on the
personal side of making content I'm on like the
icon pass content crew um also here with Altera
and we're doing a GoPro shoot here in a couple
days so we're excited to be here out there see
what we're dealing with yeah yeah for sure awesome
thanks for introducing yourselves guys and anyone
who doesn't know I'm Saran I'm the communication
specialist C so all the journalists here are kind
of like my homies um Ryland is kind of in charge
of everyone else but um yeah really nice to meet
all of you and I love that we have such like
wide range of abilities and like people who
are new to H skiing new to H in general I think
it's going to make for some really good energy
so thank you all for coming as you guys can see
there's obviously a lot of people from like all
different sort of backgrounds from journalists to
you know proos skiers to filmmakers and stuff like
that so the biggest concern with this weekend
is the temperatures Avalanche danger is quite
high it's supposed to be 50° is so I think
it's going to be kind of variable in terms
of snow conditions and what we get ourselves
into but the whole experience is kind of what
we're after should be beautiful day to get in a
helicopter up in the mountains but we are going
to do some like safety stuff so then we're kind
of set for the next few days so we're going to
learn how to kind of use beacons and whatnot
kind of this this anything that you would go
through if you were going helis skiing or cat
skiing or anything where you're like actually
in the back country so obviously danger is
way you know considerably higher and they
even said we'll probably observe quite a few
Avalanches so we're going to see how it goes
but Beautiful Day Kicking horse is like literally
right behind me so cool being up P cool actually
being able to see the mountain but day one of
H skiing stoked I've had coffee now so I'm good
to [Music] [Applause] [Music] go I believe the
helicopter holds eight people and then the guides
and whatnot so we've broken up into two groups
um and we are the first group out so we're going
to be the first group up in the hel it's like me
Abe Caleb zadia B so kind of a pretty fun little
group but like I said I think we got to be really
sort of mellow with kind of what we get ourselves
into there's a few days here so that's the deal
so safety stuff went well time to get up into the
[Music] helicopter [Music]
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah thank you [Music] man [Music] all right
well first drop off up here and it's absolutely
gorgeous stuff that you'd see like in a movie I
feel like cool today to have fun do a few runs oo
crusty wow guys
[Applause]
unbelievable
fun I'm going chase you
Lucas oh oh
yeah oh
yeah
ah that pretty nice that was sick
woo [Applause]
[Applause]
nice trust even fun we're not going to try not to
do a bunch of tree skiing today cuz it's probably
not where we're going to find a good snow but
right here short tree shot we just ski down to
that Creek that's pitch down to where the other
side meets but to good idea hey just to ski with
with the buddy in case someone goes upside down
on the tree well so if you partner up Luc Caleb
up top I think further left you work you're going
to run into less tracks i' go a little left of
mine kind of bomb through here yeah yeah what' you
say
nice call Burke wow that nice oh [Applause]
sh nice
that's
sick
oh we're so close to those
pillows can we get any of
them
I there's some little bonkers in here oh
yeah
[Applause]
0:11:59.240,1193:02:47.295
[Music]
that's sick
HP dogood all we're going to see Burke
do a little little jump first jump of
the day Snoodle that [__] top Snoodle
action we are high elevation up here we
got some softer snowood hi eln let's go Burke Bur
Jesus I shot in slowmo I didn't need to
that was insane yeah we'll we'll straight
there
Caleb that was sick work so was your everyone's
mistake
whoa
got one more run in you before
we break for lunch yeah oh
yeah [Music]
n
fire
what are you thinking Burke hit this thing
that way oh is there like a little just like
straight over it basically yeah let it go
cuz this way you got to go pretty small but
they like pretty tapered on that side hit
this little L yeah like off of this thing
straight like those trees down there oh SI
I'm going to ride I might go like just up
above you and just film you you're going to
go left yeah I'm going to like come off get
the nose coming this way and then land like
right past that little roller down there okay
then I'm I'm going to come down below you then
okay perfect I just don't want to be in your
Landing you think you're going to go on the back
side of the roller is about where you're going to
land yeah okay I'll just still stay kind of
behind you but in front if that makes sense
you good I'm
good that was so sick Jesus
dude [Music] I
[Music] I I can help the I can help the I can help
[Music]
well this is probably the most picturesque lunch
I think I've ever had I feel like we've done six
seven laps maybe but I got to be honest guys it
is way better than I thought it was going to be
I just thought with like the warm temperatures
and all that sort of stuff I thought it'd be
kind of rough but there's just something so
cool about having like a Vista like this and
then just getting basically untracked stuff and
skiing with Abe and Burke and zadius it's really
rat so let a lunch break I have a turkey sandwich
and a nice cup of soup so can't complain sick day
very warm very intense Sun but uh very impressed
with the white walkers on a day like this [Music]
[Music]
drop the
helicopter
quick on your feet over
there don't stay in there too
long hey let's go team cuz the
other group will be right on
our
nice I'm thinking I'm going
to try to jump over [Music]
it
good for a New Yorker man thank you every
day
thank
you and that's the wrap guys day one of H skiing
with CMH absolutely incredible although it feels
like it's literally 60° down here smells like
spring feels like spring so unreal day like
I said was way better than I thought super fun
and even got to get around like some fun little
like Cliff hits and all that sort of stuff so
absolutely zero complaints these are probably
some of the most beautiful mountains I've ever
been to and I'm just stoked I got to like be a
part of it out there in there and like just a
really really sort of well-run gig and yeah I
can't complain when the skiing was so creamy
So Soft oh what you think coming to interrupt
yeah what' you think uh it better than expected
that's what I said yeah I mean it's sunny being
able to see is so huge yeah it's kind of like
yikes Zia yikes feel like you can have a lot
of fun on not that steep of terrain if you can
see the snow is a little bit soft and there's
playful features I feel like that's kind of
what we found so I was pleasantly surprised
yeah sweet and the view is probably decent
cloudy today I saw one Cloud really bued me
out I love Duff bag you turn
you turned me onto the duffel
[Music] bag well sad we have the boots
charging the boots also drying out
here we have GoPro accessories and things sort
of laid out and lastly we have oh our battery uh
situation going for tomorrow since we got back to
the hotel some of us went to the hot tub then we
went to a nice dinner here down the road a kicking
horse went to the uh the bar around the corner for
a little bit did some footage exchange and now
it's time to go to sleep and do it all over again
tomorrow so very very solid day thank you so much
to CMH pcel CMH hel skiing for organizing this
whole thing and putting it on having us out here
absolute dream come true this this sort of trip
is just something I don't take for granted and
something I'm very thankful I'm grateful to be a
part of so thank you guys for watching Squad I'll
s you guys in the next episode when we do this all
again tomorrow might be skiing the same runs might
be getting into some different stuff but still
going to enjoy another day out here in British
Columbia so thanks for watching Squad peace
[Music] out
go